Get Ready for Ricki.
Ricki and the Flash is a comedy, drama, music film directed by Jonathan Demme.
Meryl Streep stars as Ricki Rendazzo, a guitar heroine who made a world of
mistakes as she followed her dreams of rock-and-roll stardom.
Returning home, Ricki gets a shot at redemption and a chance to make
things right as she faces the music with her family.
Ricki Rendazzo, played by Meryl Streep.
Pete Brummel, played by Kevin Kline.
Julie Brummel, played by Mamie Gummer.
Joshua Brummel, played by Sebastian Stan.
Maureen Brummel, played by Audra McDonald.
Daniel, played by Ben Platt.
Ricki and the Flash is a 2015 American musical comedy-drama film directed by Jonathan Demme and written by Diablo
Cody, about a woman who leaves her family to become a rock star and later gets a chance to make amends.
The film stars Meryl Streep, Mamie Gummer, Kevin Kline,
Sebastian Stan, Rick Springfield, and Audra McDonald.
The film marks Streep and Kline's third collaboration after Sophie's
Choice (1982) and A Prairie Home Companion (2006).
It was Demme's final narrative film before his death in April 2017.
Principal photography began on October 13, 2014, in Rye, New York.
TriStar Pictures financed, and released the film on August 7, 2015.
The film received mixed reviews from critics, who praised the performances of the cast but criticised its
screenplay and execution, and grossed $41 million against its $18–30 million production budget.
The film explores themes of rock star, homophobia,
aging, family relationships, divorce.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.